homeschoolmath.net 2012-10-11

# Privacy Policy of www.homeschoolmath.net

[Maria's Math news](http://www.homeschoolmath.net/newsletter/) \- a monthly FREE newsletter filled with math teaching information.

Subscribe below:

This is where you'll find the latest happenings, news, & ideas in math teaching 

My videos at YouTube show you how to teach concepts.   
[Structured drill of multiplication tables](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4bpq3Mqbwv0)—much more effective than random drill! 

Various worksheets on TONS of math topics you can generate for free! 

Advice, reviews, and resources to help you choose a math curriculum! 

Games you can play online, interactive tutorials, fun math websites and more. Arranged by topic/level for ease of use. 

Learn how to TEACH concepts or about general concerns in math education. 

In-depth reviews of math products 

A list of free message boards, math help websites, and online tutoring services. 

I have two games on my site, plus links to many.   
[Word guess game ](http://www.homeschoolmath.net/math-hangman/easy_hangman.php) (easy hangman)  
[Word guess game ](http://www.homeschoolmath.net/math-hangman/index.php) (difficult)

| 

The main activities of Homeschool Math website (www.homeschoolmath.net) is to offer free resources for mathematics teaching.

You can access and browse Homeschool Math website without disclosing any of your personal information (such as name, address, telephone number, email address, or credit card information) nor do we collect information about our visitors from any public records. 

If you voluntarily submit any information to us (especially email address), I may use that to contact you, or to answer your questions. Homeschool Math will not trade, sell or share your personal information that you voluntarily submit to us to any third party. 

Visitors can voluntarily submit their email address and name to subscribe to **HomeschoolMath Newsletter**. This service is provided by [Aweber](http://www.aweber.com/). HomeschoolMath.net will not disclose your email address to other parties.

Homeschool Math does not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.

**Statistics info:**

 **As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Cookies:** We do use cookies [on our worksheet generators](http://www.homeschoolmath.net/worksheets/) to generate a running number for the worksheets. We do not use cookies to store any other data.

**Advertisers:** I use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on HomeschoolMath.net, most notably Amazon.com and Google. These advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information about your IP address, your ISP, your browser, whether you have Flash installed, and about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This information is not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off the third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. You may may opt out of the use of Google's DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

To see Amazon's and Google's privacy policies, click here: [Amazon.com Privacy Notice](http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/tg/browse/-/468496/102-6533223-3461729) or [Google Ads Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

The website is owned and maintained by Maria Miller. If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact me here.

** | 

**New!** Times Tales is now [on DVD](http://www.1shoppingcart.com/app/?Clk=4082494)!

The fast, FUN, and easy way to learn multiplication. Learn the upper times tales in two sittings using mnemonic stories.
